Hi, I have got 5+ years of experience working with Python. I have got hands on experience in Computer Vision and Deep Learning models and NLP. I see you are in urgent need to hire someone for your project which makes me a perfect candidate for this job because I can start working asap.

>> I can work with following Computer Vision Techniques:

- Image Classification

- Object Detection

- Object Tracking

- Semantic Segmentation

- Instance Segmentation

>> I am familiar with following deep learning techniques:

- Classic Neural Networks

- Convolutional Neural Networks

>> I have worked on many NLP applications such as:

- Sentiment analysis

- Chatbot Systems

- Question answering systems

>> I am familiar working with following NLP machine learning algorithms:

- Support Vector Machines

- Bayesian Networks

- Maximum Entropy

- Conditional Random Field

- Neural Networks/Deep Learning


Kindly, share the project details or we can discuss over a call whenever you're free, just hit me up.

Thanks!

Looking forward to hearing from you soon!