Hi, I have got 5+ years of experience working with Machine Learning projects. I have got hands on experience in Natural Language Processing. I see you are in urgent need to hire someone for your project which makes me a perfect candidate for this job because I can start working asap.

>> I have worked on many NLP applications such as:

Sentiment analysis

Chatbot Systems

Question answering systems

>> I am familiar working with following NLP machine learning algorithms:

Support Vector Machines

Bayesian Networks

Maximum Entropy

Conditional Random Field

Neural Networks/Deep Learning

Kindly, share the project details or we can discuss over a call whenever you're free, just hit me up.

Thanks!

Looking forward to hearing from you soon!